Guide to the Ithaca Rotary Club Records, 1914-2016.
Ithaca Rotary Club Records
- Series VIII. Rotary International
  - Publications
    - Convention Proceedings, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Convention Proceedings, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Official Directory, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Official Directory, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Official Directory, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Official Directory, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Official Directory, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Official Directory, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Official Directory, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Official Directory, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Rotary?, 1934 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - This Rotarian Age, 1935 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - The Outline of Classifications, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Service is My Business, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - From a Yankee Notebook, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - From a Yankee Notebook in Taiwan, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Seven Paths to Peace, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Rotary: Fifty Years of Service, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Misc Pamphlets, R.I., 1955-1995 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Series IX. Multimedia
  Contains DVD’s, CD's, floppy disks, a videocassette, and a phonograph record. The DVD’s include a series of Oral History interviews conducted with Ithaca Rotary Members in 2004. Interviewees include Jack Burns, Bob Eastman, Barbara Caldwell, Carman Hill, Gene Erickson, Bob and Dale Baker, John Seeley and Bob Yong, Dale Flinn, Dave Flinn, Barbara Thuesen, Barlow Ware, Don Kompf, Bill Downing, and Fred Antil.
  - Oral Histories (8 DVD's), 2004; DVD-1458-1465 (Box 25)
  - New Orleans/Hurricane Katrina (5 DVD's), 2005-2007; DVD-1466 & CD-2434-2437 (Box 25)
  - Lagniappe Presbyterian Church trip, 2007; CD-2438 (Box 25)
  - Other Rotary pictures, 2008-2014; CD-2439 (Box 25)
  - Passing the Gavel DVD, June 28 2006; DVD-1467 (Box 25)
  - Rotary Harvest, Undated; DVD-1468 (Box 25)
  - Dopyera Violin, 2005; DVD-1469 (Box 25)
  - Caitlin in Bolivia, 2005; DVD-1470 (Box 25)
  - Rotary Foundation movie, 2014; DVD-1471 (Box 25)
  - Rotary Floppy Disks (2 disks), Undated; FD-60 & FD-61 (Box 25)
  - Rotary Meeting Video, June 25 2003; V-8300 (Box 25)
  - Rotary Phonograph Record, 1939; SR-6471
  - Rotary Harvest, Undated; CD-3569
- Series X. Photographs
  Includes labeled and unlabeled photographs, both loose and in albums. Includes both black and white and color shots.
  - Adams, Arthur (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Alexander, Earle (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Allen, Fay E. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Anderson, Walfred A. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Atkinson, Earl (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Atwood, Sanford S. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Babcock, H. E. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Baker, Bert (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Bliss, Seward (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Blomgren, Elmer (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Boothroyd, Robert S. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Boutwell, (Rev) A. H (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Bradfield, Richard (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Brand, Walter (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Brooks, John G. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Brown, Fred (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Brown, W. D. (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Bruckner, J. H. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Brundage, G. F. (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Burgan, John L. (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Burns, John C. (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Burns, Wm. H. (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Butler, Karl H. (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Cass, Leon H. (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Champlain, (Dr.) O. K. (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Chandler, John (Box 27, Folder 25a)
  - Chaney, C. E. (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Cook, G. Louis (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Cooper, R. B. (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Corcoran, Wm. B (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Coryell, Jay (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Cosentini, Joseph (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Couch, Harvey J. (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Courtney, John (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Corfoot, James (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Crone, James M. (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Crowley, (Dr.) ? (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Crum, H. H. (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Curry, Merrill (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Curtis, C. E. (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Curtis, Otis F. (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Dall, Albert C. (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Dallenbach, Karl M. (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Dahlberg, Arthur C. (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Danks, A. G. (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - DeMotte, Earl A. (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - De Grassi, George (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Devericks, Robert (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - De Young, Ben B. (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - Dietrich, Henry (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Dillon, W. A. (Bill) (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Dodds, W. A. (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Downey, J. J. C. (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Fagan, Charles F. (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Fahey, George B. (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Fallon, E. J. (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Fallon, Frank (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Fear, (Dr.) ? (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Finney, Glenn E. (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Forbes, N. M. (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Fossum, M. Truman (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Frank, George (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Fried, Jerome A. (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Frost, (Dr.) Joseph (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Frost, James (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Frostie, Wm. J. (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - Gaurnier, Larry (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Geer, W. C. (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Gibb, Arthur N. (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Gillette, Douglas (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - Gordon, Harry (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Graham, E. K. (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - Hagan, W. A. (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - Hanks, Elton K. (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - Hanselman, George R. (Box 27, Folder 74)
  - Harris, S. O. (maybe G. D.) (Box 27, Folder 75)
  - Hart, Van (Box 27, Folder 76)
  - Helverson, Ralph (Box 27, Folder 77)
  - Herron, Paul (Box 27, Folder 78)
  - Hewitt, Douglas (Box 27, Folder 79)
  - Hill, Forest F. (Box 27, Folder 80)
  - Hodges, Harry G. (Box 27, Folder 81)
  - Holland, Wm. (Box 27, Folder 82)
  - Hospital, Ralph (Box 27, Folder 83)
  - Howlan, Harry (Box 27, Folder 84)
  - Hurd, T. Norman (Box 27, Folder 85)
  - Job, Leonard (Box 27, Folder 86)
  - Johnson, A. A. (Box 27, Folder 87)
  - Jones, H. C. (Box 27, Folder 88)
  - Kane, Robert (Box 27, Folder 89)
  - Kelsey, L. D. (Box 27, Folder 90)
  - Kenerson, Charles (Box 27, Folder 91)
  - King, Asa A. (Box 27, Folder 92)
  - King, H. J. (Box 27, Folder 93)
  - Kingsley, Ralph, R. (Box 27, Folder 94)
  - Klaer, Alfred Lee (Box 27, Folder 95)
  - Kruse, Paul J. (Box 27, Folder 96)
  - Kulp, Claude (Box 27, Folder 97)
  - Laube, H. D. (Box 27, Folder 98)
  - Laux, John D. (Box 27, Folder 99)
  - Lincoln, Stanley (Box 27, Folder 100)
  - Loberg, Harry J. (Box 27, Folder 101)
  - Love, H. H. (Box 27, Folder 102)
  - Lumbard, Reginald (Box 27, Folder 103)
  - MacDaniels, L. H. (Box 27, Folder 104)
  - Morton, Stewart (Box 27, Folder 105)
  - McGurk, C. (Box 27, Folder 106)
  - Maughan, George H. (Box 27, Folder 107)
  - Meek, Howard B. (Box 27, Folder 108)
  - Meigs, Robert B. (Box 27, Folder 109)
  - Mendenhall, Wm. H. (Box 27, Folder 110)
  - Mitchell, C. W. (Box 27, Folder 111)
  - Monroe, Benton S. (Box 27, Folder 112)
  - Moore, Clyde B. (Box 27, Folder 113)
  - Morris, Evan J. (Box 27, Folder 113a)
  - Morrison, Frank (Box 27, Folder 114)
  - Morse, Clarence (Box 27, Folder 115)
  - Milks, Howard (Box 27, Folder 116)
  - Mumsey, W. A. (Box 27, Folder 117)
  - Murphy, R. P. (Box 27, Folder 118)
  - Murray, Harry (Box 27, Folder 119)
  - Nettles, C. P. (Box 27, Folder 120)
  - Newman, Charles H. (Box 27, Folder 121)
  - Niedeck, A. E. (Box 27, Folder 122)
  - Norris, Glenn (Box 27, Folder 123)
  - Olson, (Dr.) ? (Box 27, Folder 124)
  - Osbeck, C. B. (Box 27, Folder 125)
  - Osbourne, R. C. (Box 27, Folder 126)
  - Palmer, E. L. (Box 27, Folder 127)
  - Perkins, H. C. (Box 27, Folder 128)
  - Peters, H. M. (Box 27, Folder 129)
  - Peterson, A. H. (Box 27, Folder 130)
  - Petzold, Harry (Box 27, Folder 131)
  - Pollock, R. L. (Box 27, Folder 132)
  - Powers, Truman K. (Box 27, Folder 133)
  - Pratt, Harold (Box 27, Folder 134)
  - Price, Don (Box 27, Folder 135)
  - Pritchard, Leon (Box 27, Folder 136)
  - Pritchard, Wm. (Box 27, Folder 137)
  - Ranney, W. A. (?) (Box 27, Folder 138)
  - Reed, Harold L. (Box 27, Folder 139)
  - Richardson, J. R. (Box 27, Folder 140)
  - Robinson, C. S. (Box 27, Folder 141)
  - Roehl, Lewis M. (Box 27, Folder 142)
  - Rogalsky, Fred A. (Box 27, Folder 143)
  - Romanoff, Alexis (Box 27, Folder 144)
  - Rothschild, James (Box 27, Folder 145)
  - Rothschild, Leon. (Box 27, Folder 146)
  - Sadd, C. W. (Box 27, Folder 147)
  - Sailor, R. Warren (Box 27, Folder 148)
  - Sovocool, Benjamin F. (Box 27, Folder 149)
  - Sawdon, Wm. M. (Box 27, Folder 150)
  - Schatz, Maurice H. (Box 27, Folder 151)
  - Schwartz, Edward (Box 27, Folder 152)
  - Scott, Wm. M., Jr (Box 27, Folder 153)
  - Shackelton, Horace E. (Box 27, Folder 154)
  - Shirey, Henry (Box 27, Folder 155)
  - Shipher, T. M. (Box 27, Folder 156)
  - Slaughter, Elwyn S. (Box 27, Folder 157)
  - Smith, Charles E. (Box 27, Folder 158)
  - Smith, Elwood W. (Box 27, Folder 159)
  - Smith, Louis P (Box 27, Folder 160)
  - Smith, Ralph C. (Box 27, Folder 161)
  - Smith, Sheldon (Box 27, Folder 161a)
  - Snyder, Clarence (Box 27, Folder 162)
  - Somers, G. Fred (Box 27, Folder 163)
  - Space, Ralph (Box 27, Folder 164)
  - Spence, Leland (Box 27, Folder 165)
  - Spaid, F. O. (Box 27, Folder 166)
  - Stephenson, C. Hadley (Box 27, Folder 167)
  - Stewart, Rolland M. (Box 27, Folder 168)
  - Taber, Paul (Box 27, Folder 169)
  - Tallcott, R. A. (Box 27, Folder 170)
  - Thomas, C. W. (Box 27, Folder 171)
  - Thomas, H. A. (Box 27, Folder 172)
  - Tilton, John M. (Box 27, Folder 173)
  - Tinker, Martin B., Sr (Box 27, Folder 174)
  - Tinker, Martin Jr. (Box 27, Folder 175)
  - Treman, Allen H. (Box 27, Folder 176)
  - Treman, Robert (Box 27, Folder 177)
  - Underwood, E. Victor (Box 27, Folder 178)
  - Underwood, F. O. (Box 27, Folder 179)
  - Van Lent, L. M. J. (Box 27, Folder 180)
  - Ward, Wm. B (Box 27, Folder 181)
  - Watkins, Gordon (Box 27, Folder 182)
  - Weaver, L. E. (Box 27, Folder 183)
  - Wetherlow, Huge E. (Box 27, Folder 184)
  - Wiggans, Roy G. (Box 27, Folder 185)
  - Wilcox, Harold (Box 27, Folder 186)
  - Wilkinson, Wm. P. (Box 27, Folder 187)
  - Williams, J. Walter (Box 27, Folder 188)
  - Wilson, Lyman (Box 27, Folder 189)
  - Winans, R. R. (Box 27, Folder 190)
  - Wing, Ralph (Box 27, Folder 191)
  - Woodcock, Fletcher (Box 27, Folder 191a)
  - Wordon, Harold E. (Box 27, Folder 192)
  - Wright, Forrest B. (Box 27, Folder 193)
  - Young, Charles V. P. (Box 27, Folder 194)
  - Pancake Day Album, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Unlabeled Group (Russian Exchange?), 1994 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Photos and Journal Story on Fall Creek Park (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Ithaca Rotary Club, 1928 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - 50 Year Anniversary Dinner (Statler), 1964 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Photos by C. Hadley Smith
  - Claude Kulp--1960's? (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - B&W Photographs. Paul Harris Fellows? (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Rotary Album, 1985-1992 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Pearlington, MS/Katrina Album, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - 1997 Album, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Gray album 1, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Gray album 2, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Football team (kids) (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Color Photos (Student Exchange?) (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - John P Young Portrait and Negatives (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Found with material from the 1970's
  - Ithaca Interact Charter Night, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Taughannock Park Breakfast, Early 1930's (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Individuals labeled
  - Foundation Dinner (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Christmas Program (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - D.A.R.E. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Ithaca Festival Parade, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Oliver Jones (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - 1995 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - 75th or 80th Anniversary, 1989-1994 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Club's 80th Year, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Jean McPheters, Pass the Gavel (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Committees and Cabinets (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Pancake Day incl. negatives (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - R.Y.L.A., 1996 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Rotary Events, 1985-1997 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Misc Wallet-Sized (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Unknown Celebration (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Unknown, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Unknown Event (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Misc. B&W (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Misc. Photos (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Misc. Portraits, 1990s (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Unknown Event (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Barbecue, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Ithaca Yacht Club, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Pancake Day, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Portraits, 1990s or 2000s (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Pass the Gavel, Heidi Goldstein, Undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Group in hard-hats, Undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Unknown 2006 events, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Unknown 2007 events, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Rotary banner display, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - International Youth Exchange program Discover America Bus Tour photo albums, 1977-06-27-1977-07-19 (Box 40)
- Series XI. Memorabilia and Ephemera
  Objects such as plaques, certificates, Paul Harris Fellow Medals, Barlow Ware’s whistle, and other artifacts.
  - Certificates: Ithaca Rotary, 1963-2009 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Rotary Mementos, 1964-1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Ithaca Rotary Programs, 1924-1928 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Songs of the Rotary Club of Ithaca, NY, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Four-Way Test, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 40th Anniversary Material, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - 50th Anniversary Programs, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Club History for 50th Anniversary, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Clippings--Banner Display, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - 75th Anniversary Tickets--signed, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1980s (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Misc. Clippings (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 2000-2007 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Plaque: Rotary Foundation, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Salvation Army Plaques, 1969-1979 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Placards: "Remember 66 for 66" (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Paper bag: "Stop DWI" (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Rotary Badge, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Paul Harris Fellow Medals (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Rotary Flags (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Barlow Ware's Whistle (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Ithaca Rotary type and stamps (box) (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Rotary Golf Tournament award, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Candle holder? (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Mounted Rotary Foundation Award (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Framed Polio Award, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Oversized certificates and posters, 1964-2008 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 75 Years of Service oversize plaque, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Four-Way Test oversize framed poster, 1946 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Pride of Ownership award oversize framed award, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Roteract Club Cornell University oversize framed certificate, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Files relating to awards, 2011-2012 (Box 32)
  - Group study tour to Taiwan, 2013 (Box 32)
  - Misc. publications (Box 32)
  - commemorative medallions, 1984-1985; MU-2071 (Box 32)
  - Clippings, 2004, 2014 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Road Rally, 2014 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Peace Through Service award, 2012-2013 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Speech - passing the gavel, Brian to Heidi, Undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Bettsie Park - Rotary Club active member pin [MU-2265], Undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Newspapers, 2011-2015 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Road rally scavenger hunt, 2015 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Additional certificates, 2013-2015 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Gifts and donations (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Misc. items (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - 3 items that appear to be medals/awards, 2011-2015 (Box 25)
  - Polio Plus campaign certificate, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Presidential Citation, 1994-1995, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Rotary Youth Leadership Awards Conference, 2015 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Membership Development Award, Undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Charter Night program, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Cards/invitations, 2006, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Certificates, 2007-2011 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Plaque - "For Service Above and Beyond", 1989-2010 (Box 37)
  - Framed acknowledgement of Ithaca Rotary as a 10,000% Club (from the Trustees of the Rotary Foundation), 1987-1988 (Box 37)
  - The Rotary Code of Ethics (at very bottom of box), Undated (Box 37)
  - Service award materials, 2008-2013 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Pride of Workmanship Award nominations, 2015-2016 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Pride of Workmanship Award materials, 2008-2012 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Career and Tech services awards, 2004-2008 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - James L. Gibbs Scholarship materials, 2003-2010 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Various awards documents, letters, and pamphlets, 2008-2012 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Ithaca Rotary Club Centennial ideas, 2012 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Rotary Club pins, Undated; MU-1902-1912 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Scarf, Undated; MU-1913 (Box 40)